Oh, hey there. I'm Amanda Seals, and this is The Amanda Seals Show. Yeah, so on my show,
we talk about all types of things, whether it's news and current events, pop culture,
lifestyle, just giving y'all information. The other thing that happens on The Amanda
Seals Show is I share my opinions, the information I've learned, and my own experiences. You
know why? Because it's my show. That's right. So if you're here in the comments to complain
about me talking about myself on my own show named after me, then baby, you're in the wrong place.
I know, it's crazy. Yeah, and I know celebrity culture has folks feeling like they can talk
about people any way they want, wherever they want, when they want, but that's not how we operate
here at The Amanda Seals Show. So if you come at me sideways in these comments, we will block you.
We're here cultivating community, so you can keep that toxic crap in your group chat.
All right, I hope we cleared that up. I want you to be listening to us every day. You can check us
out wherever you get your podcasts, and we're syndicated in select cities. Join us to listen,
laugh, and learn at The Amanda Seals Show. That's me.
Mm-hmm.